Elvia Franco

About

Organized, creative and diligent team player with 3+ years' experience in analytical, project management and process improvement-oriented roles. Seeking to advance career by utilizing and expanding knowledge of project management and data analysis to provide excellent solutions and become a positive and contributing collaborator and go-getter!

Skills

Microsoft Office

Strategic Planning

Process Improvement

Project Management

Data Analysis

Interests

Hanging out with my shih-tzus Mei and Moo, staying curious and learning new skills! Currently taking several fun courses in web development, graphic design and UI/UX design using Adobe XD.

Contact

T: 480-263-2754

evfranco@asu.edu linkedin.com/in/elviafranco

Scottsdale, Arizona

Education

Master of Science, Management	
School of Public Affairs, Arizona State University	
Bachelor of Science, Public Service & Public Policy	2013
Certificate, Public Administration & Public Management	

Experience

Advisor, Regulatory Affairs CVS Health, Scottsdale, AZ

2017-Present

2017

 Execute processes improvement solutions by regularly reviewing potential collaboration points and leading internal work groups to develop projects that focus on standardizing and streamlining key functions/operational processes within the Regulatory Affairs department.

W. P. Carey School of Business, Arizona State University

- Oversee the Regulatory communications for executive communications, including owning KPIs, metrics, and dashboards.
- Track regulation implementation projects weekly and lead bi-weekly status calls with business owners to track project performance for the Medicaid, Exchange, and Commercial lines of business.
- Provide Archer database reporting support by pulling and distributing reports and supporting system enhancements by building requirements documentation and performing testing.

Jr. Business Applications Analyst Voya Investment Management, Scottsdale, AZ

2015-2016

- Responsible for planning, implementing, and closing business application projects while providing ongoing CRM maintenance.
- Worked with various vendors and coordinated with business clients to collect business requirements that can be translated into technical requirements.
- Responsible for analyzing various types of data or processes and providing feedback on results.
- Assists with any testing relating to projects and enhancements while assisting with ad hoc inquiries from business units and resolving issues with data upload failures.
- Developed batch files and used Cisco Tidal Enterprise Scheduler to automate and ensure that daily files were uploaded and processed properly into business application.
- Successfully loaded SMA equity sales reporting data from financial service firms into SalesPage CRM to better assist our Corporate Finance team with the calculation of commissions.

Experience

Marketing Communications Specialist Northcentral University, Scottsdale, AZ

2015-2015

- Implement and manage content requirements of offline and online marketing and communication initiatives for the University.
- Assisted with managing the content and maintenance of the University's Social Media channels including
 daily interaction and monitoring of all social media vehicles and their respective metrics and reporting
 responsibilities (Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Blogs, etc.)
- Analyzed social media trends and recommend changes to marketing, enrollment, and strategic partnership strategies based on analysis and feedback.
- Executes email communication through a marketing automation system for University communication as well as working closely on email nurturing programs.
- Responsible for ensuring brand messages are consistent throughout the University community and across all media platforms.

Marketing Coordinator, Northcentral University, Scottsdale, AZ

2014-2015

- Responsible for the management of operational workflow of new programs, job requests, campaigns, and other initiatives.
- Supports the marketing team with campaign creation in marketing automation systems while managing inventory of assets.
- Responsible for supporting creative, digital and analyst marketing team members to assist with the formulation and execution of marketing strategies.
- Performed billing, invoicing and reconciliation for marketing-related expenses.
- Assisted with research and competitive analysis projects and requests.
- Assisted with event planning including the annual graduation event, symposia, open houses, and other relevant events.

Administrative Assistant/Campus Support Northcentral University, Scottsdale, AZ

2013-2014

- Responsible for leading preparation, coordination and implementation of key projects that are relevant to the executive team.
- Conducted research while analyzing data for report and document preparation.
- Responsible for calendar coordination and scheduling of the executive team.
- Performed a variety of facilities related tasks such as ordering supplies, issuing purchase orders and stocking inventory.

Administrative Assistant City of Tempe - Public Works, Tempe, AZ

2012-2013

- Performed a variety of routine clerical work including: filing, billing and record maintenance.
- Responsible for payroll processing and purchasing information such as ordering of office supplies and materials while compiling and processing invoice orders.
- Coordinated and maintained calendars and schedules for meetings, activities, and events with outside agencies and City of Tempe personnel.
- Responsible for providing written procedures, agenda packets, and transcriptions of meeting minutes.